Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Art Practice
  - Subseries B: Writing
    - Letters from Linda: Chapter Lists, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Linda Montano: Completed 3rd Draft [1 of 2], November 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Letters from Linda Montano: Completed 3rd Draft [2 of 2], November 2002 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Fairy Tales, 2002, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Letters from Linda: Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Letters from Linda Almost Complete: Interviews of Linda M. Montano, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Performance Texts, Video/CD Texts, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Letters from Linda Permissions, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Personal Writings, 2002, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Poetry, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Proposals, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Statements, 2002, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Letters from Linda Complete: Teaching, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 2, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 3, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 4, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 5, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 6, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 1: Chapter 7, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 2, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 3, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 4, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 5, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 6, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Linda Montano Draft 2: Chapter 7, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of 14 Years of Living Art, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Death, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Elders, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Fairy Tales, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Interviews, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Poetry, November 2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Teaching, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Letters from Linda: Edited out of Writings, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: 14 Years of Living Art, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Dad, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Death, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Death / The Body, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Ecstasy of St. Rose, February 24, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Fairy Tales, 2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Interviews, 2001-2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Poetry, August 2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Teaching, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Tenure, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Letters from Linda Extras: Writing, 2001-2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Letters from Linda: Rationale for Book Publication, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Letters from Linda: Writings by Linda M. Montano, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Linda Mary Montano: Always Creative, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Linda M. Montano Performance History, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "Little Linda Becomes Performance Artist Chicken Linda Becomes Roman Catholic Linda Mary", undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "Littleton Colorado and Performance Art", 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "Living Art: Time Spent Artfully Alone or Not Alone", 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - "Looking at Life and Art", 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Love Sex Galley [1 of 2], September 15, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Love Sex Galley [2 of 2], September 15, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Love Sex Galley, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Love Sex Galley, September 12, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Love Sex Stories, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Meditation/Performance Teaching, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Meditation, Spirituality, Performance, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous handwritten writings, 1962-2013 (Box 14, Folder 13A)
    - Mitchell's Death, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Moments of Consciousness at New Music America: Chicago, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Montano on Hazing, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Music, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "My Astral History", undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Note to Magda, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Notebook: "Dreams and Messages", undated (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Older is Bolder: Notes from the ELDERS Workshop, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Omichi", 2007 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Once Upon A Time...", undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - One-Year Performance, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Performance and the Bay Area in the '70s", undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "Performance Artists Talking: 1979-1989", undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Artists' Biographies, Info, and Correspondence, 1998, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Artists' Interview and Photo Releases, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Book Proposal and Reader's Report, July 2001, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Book Section Introductions, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Correspondence and Interview Releases, 1997, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Correspondence with Jane McFadden, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Cover Mock-ups and Promotional Material, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Performance Artists Talking Drafts: Title Page, Section Pages, Introductions, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Drafts of Interviews: Food, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Drafts of Interviews: Money/Fame, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Drafts of Interviews: Ritual/Death, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Drafts of Interviews: Sex, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Early Interviews, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Editing Draft [1 of 3], June 20, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Editing Draft [2 of 3], June 20, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Editing Draft [3 of 3], June 20, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Performance Artists Talking: First Edit from Routledge [1 of 2], January 10, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Performance Artists Talking: First Edit from Routledge [2 of 2], January 10, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Food Annotated Draft, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Food Interviews: Final, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Food Intro, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Food Originals, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Interview Releases, Book Proposal, Reader Reviews, 1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking in the '80s Galleys, 1994, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Last Edit from Routledge [1 of 2], June 12, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Last Edit from Routledge [2 of 2], June 12, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Money/Fame: Annotated Draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Money/Fame: Interviews, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Money/Fame Interviews: Final, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Money/Fame Originals, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: The Performance Bible Bound Draft: Money/Fame, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking: The Performance Bible Bound Draft: Ritual/Death, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Performance Bible Final Draft, July 27, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Performance Artists Talking: The Performance Bible: Food Galley, January 25, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: The Performance Bible: Ritual/Death Galley, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: The Performance Bible: Sex Galley, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Photos of Interviewees [1 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Photos of Interviewees [2 of 2], undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Hi-Res Photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death: Annotated Draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death: Corrected and Printed Final [1 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death: Corrected and Printed Final [2 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death Interviews [1 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death Interviews [2 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death Originals [1 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Ritual/Death Originals [2 of 2], undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Sex: Annotated Draft, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Sex: Corrected and Printed Final, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Performance Artists Talking: Sex Originals, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Performance Artists Talking: "Talking Artists", undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Performance Artists Talking: University of California Press Packet, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "Performance as Healing", October 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "Performance in the '80s", 1978, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - "The Performance of Montano's Shoe Store", 2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Performance Texts/Video Texts Bound Draft, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Persona Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Post-Menopausal Cards/Photo, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Questions for Womens Caucus for the Arts, October 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Rose Moon, March 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Sacred Sex, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Sacred Sex draft, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Sacred Sex Galley, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Mock-up for Sacred Sex [1 of 2], undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Mock-up for Sacred Sex [2 of 2], undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Sacred Sex Stories, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Sacred Sex Stories, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "Search", undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication", undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - "Sex, Fear and the Catholic Church", June 1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Sister Joan, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Sister Rosita Summer Saint Camp: Promotional Materials, Correspondence, 1987, 1989, 1991, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - "Statement", undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - "Subconscious Re-Doing", undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - The Story of Illegal Mexicans and their Legal Children in America, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - The Story of Sharada, wife of Ramakrishna, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "Teaching Performance", 1981, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "Thoughts on Performance Art/A Performance Art Time Line", August 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Three Interactive/Performative: Slide Lectures by Linda M. Montano [1 of 2], 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Three Interactive/Performative: Slide Lectures by Linda M. Montano [2 of 2], 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "Time for a Poem", 2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - "Time in General", undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Video Quartet, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - "Why Computation is Like Meditation", undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - "Window Peace", undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - "The Women's Movement and the Arts", July 1977 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Writing from Fred Poales Class, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Writing Tour Papers, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - You Too Are a Performance Artist: Draft, with Photos [1 of 2], undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - You Too Are a Performance Artist: Draft, with Photos [2 of 2], undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - You Too Are a Performance Artist: Notes and Galley, 2011-2013 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Subseries C: Interviews
    Subseries C includes interviews Montano conducted for her book project entitled Performance Artists Talking in the '80s. It also contains material related to interviews of Montano by others for articles, both published and unpublished.
    - Address Book for Interviews, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Compiled Interviews with Linda Montano, 1999-2001, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Interview by Alex & Allyson Grey, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Interview by Arturo, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Interview by Carolee Schneemann, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Interview by Charles Duncan at the Brooklyn Rail, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Scope and Contents
      See oversize for separated material.
    - Interview by Cynthia Carr, July 10, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Interview by David Gunn, November 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Interview by Hilary Robinson, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Interview by Jenni Sorkin, December 7, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Interview by Jennie Klein, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Interview by Lisa Weintraub, August 2004 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Interview by M. Ryan Noble, February 12, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Interview by Moira Roth, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Interview by Paul Couillard, February 1, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Interview by Satori, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Interview by Terri Cohn, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Interview with Alec Duffy, April 26, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Interview with Ex-Zen Monk, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Interview with Karen Finley, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - "Interview with Linda Montano, Performance Artist", September 2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Interview with Mary Lachman, [2010] (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Interview with Montano for CAA, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Interview with Tara Geer, December 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - "Linda Montano: Art in Everyday Life", January 9, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Montano Interviewed by Others, undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Montano Interviews Head Cook at Zen Arts Center, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Montano Interviews Other Artists, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Preliminary Interview Questions, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - RE/SEARCH Issue 13: Angry Women, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - U-Turn: Montano Interviews Willoughby Sharp, Vito Acconci, Karen Finley, and Alan Kaprow, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Unpublished Interviews, undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Subseries D: Research
    Subseries D contains mostly handwritten research and articles on a variety of subjects that informed Montano's art/life practices. Her research also serves as an extension of her art documentation. Themes include spirituality, astrology, health, religion, grief, meditation, and music.
    - Anorexia Nervosa Research, 1982, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Art/Life Research, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Art Therapy, 1986, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Astrology Notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bach Flower Remedies, 1983, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Bates Eye Exercises, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Bhajans: Swami Dayananda Saraswati, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Cancer, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Chakra Research, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Chakras, 1992, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Chakras Research Notes and Notepad, 2008, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - CHUD, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Contemplative Outreach of Orange County at St. Andrew's Research House, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Death and Health Research, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Densal Magazine, 1984-1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Dystonia Dialogue Magazine, 2007-2012 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Dystonia Research [1 of 2], 2006, 2007, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Dystonia Research [2 of 2], 2006, 2007, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Dystonia Spasmodic Torticollis Magazine, 2008-2013 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Economy and Catholicism, October 7, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - The Elizabeth Kubler-Ross Center, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Epic: A Journey Through Church History, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Family and Caregiving, 2008, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Grief Research, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Handbook for Building Homes of Earth, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Healing and Healthcare, 1993, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - The Healing Tao Journal, Spring 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Health and Feelings Research [1 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Health and Feelings Research [2 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Health and Feelings Research [3 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Health and Feelings Research [4 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Health and Feelings Research [5 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Health and Feelings Research [6 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Health and Feelings Research [7 of 7], 1991-2008 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Health Herbs, 1990-1991, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - History of Performance Book from Rose Cee Goldberg, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Home Improvements, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Inquiring Mind, 1986-1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Insight, Spring 1994 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - The Kalacakra Empowerment, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Karate Research, 1978-1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Meditation [1 of 4], undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Meditation [2 of 4], undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Meditation [3 of 4], undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Meditation [4 of 4], undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Menopause, 1990, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Mercy of God Prayer Center Manual, 1998, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1972-1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Neurology Now Magazine, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Performance Art Articles, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Piano Music, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Prayers and Praying Binder [1 of 2], 2000-2006, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Prayers and Praying Binder [2 of 2], 2000-2006, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Radio, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Sansho Aikido Journal of the USAF Western Region, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - School for Spiritual Growth and Inner Healing Binder [1 of 3], 1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - School for Spiritual Growth and Inner Healing Binder [2 of 3], 1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - School for Spiritual Growth and Inner Healing Binder [3 of 3], 1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Sex, Chakras, Tantra, 1986, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Shri Ramamurti International Center: ISCA Bulletin, Summer 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Snow Lion Newsletter and Catalog, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Songs, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Spirit Daily Binder, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Spirit Tours, 1998-2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Stress, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3a)
    - T'ai Chi Research, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Ten Directions, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Tibetan Ritual and Medicine, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - The To Do Institute, 2001, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Universal Life Church, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - The Vajradhatu Sun, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Vedic Interpretation Profile for Linda Montano, July 27, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 9a)
    - Volunteer Training Manual: Hospice Association of Ulster County, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Where to Acupuncture, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Yoga Nidri, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Subseries E: Press
    This subseries tracks press about Montano's career from the 1970s to the early 2000s. It includes promotional postcards, advertisements, and press releases. It also contains newspaper clippings, reviews and articles written about her art and performances, from publications like High Performance Magazine to the New York Times.
    - Advertisement, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Blank Postcards, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Book Publicity, 2011, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Business Cards, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications, 1970-1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [1 of 2], 1980-1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [2 of 2], 1980-1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [1 of 3], 1990-1999 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [2 of 3], 1990-1999 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [3 of 3], 1990-1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [1 of 5], 2000-2009 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [2 of 5], 2000-2009 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [3 of 5], 2000-2009 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [4 of 5], 2000-2009 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [5 of 5], 2000-2009 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [1 of 3], 2010-2013 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [2 of 3], 2010-2013 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications [3 of 3], 2010-2013 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Catalogs, Magazines, Publications, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases, 1975-2001, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Promotional Material, 1960-1965 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Promotional Material, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Promotional Material [1 of 3], 1980-1989 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Material [2 of 3], 1980-1989 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Promotional Material [3 of 3], 1980-1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Promotional Material [1 of 2], 1990-1999 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Promotional Material [2 of 2], 1990-1999 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Promotional Material [1 of 2], 2000-2013 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Promotional Material [2 of 2], 2000-2013 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Promotional Material, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Promotional Material (Religious), 2010, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Promotional Postcards, 1965, 1970-1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Promotional Postcards, 1980-1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Postcards, 1990-1999 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Promotional Postcards, 2000-2013 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Promotional Postcards, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Promotional Posters, 1983, 1993, 2000, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Reviews, 1970-2011 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Reviews, 1970-2011 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Reviews, 1970-2011 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Reviews, 1970-2011 (Box 36, Folder 2)